Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Резино-Резиновая Базука!
Retreat for now, men!
Отступаем, парни!
Everyone! Find any way out you can!
Ребята! Ищите пути отхода!
– Wait for us!
Подождите!
Did we all make it?!
Все на местах?
Are the people you were with when you got off the ship here?!
Оглядитесь, все ли вернулись?
Yes!
На месте!
Yeah.
На месте.
Yep!
Да!
Captain Buggy isn't...
Капитана Багги...
Captain Buggy isn't here!
Капитана Багги нет!
Alright!
Отлично!
I've finally finished my flashy raft!
Наконец мой яркий плот готов!
Go!
Вперёд!
Set sail!
В путь!
What's with this crap so soon?!
Что уже за неприятности?!
I refuse to lose! Damn you!
Приключения команды Багги
I'm gonna eat you!
Сожру!
Part-Part Cannon!
Дели-Дели Пушка!
Quit struggling!
Не сопротивляйся!
Just accept your fate!
Прими свою судьбу!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Прости! Извини!
Forgive me!
Простите!
C'mon! C'mon!
Ну, же! Ну, же!
My plan is foolproof!
План просто идеален!
Dummy! Dummy! Dummy!
Дурак! Дурак! Дурак!
I caught him!
Попался!
I'm caught?! Huh?! What?!
Или это я попался?!
How did things turn out this way?!
Почему всё так обернулось?!
Stop! Stop! Ow, ow, ow!
Стойте, стойте!
Is the end here already?!
Здесь я встречу свой конец?!
Stop–
Не на—
Where am I now?
Где это я?
Leave this place!
Уходи!
Who's there?!
Кто там?!
Begone from this island at once if you value your life!
Немедленно покинь этот остров, если тебе дорога жизнь!
What are these things?
Что это такое?!
The animals of this forest.
Животные этого леса.
Don't mess with them unless you want to die!
Не связывайся с ними, если не хочешь умереть!
These animals are pretty flashy and interesting...
Эти животные такие яркие и интересные...
I told you not to go any farther!
Я ведь велел тебе не двигаться!
Blast it!
Вот чёрт!
He snuck a shot at me!
Он выстрелил в меня!
Damn! I missed!
Промахнулся!..
There you are!
Вот ты где!
What is this?!
Что такое?!
Gotcha!
Попался!
Come out!
Вылезай!
Dammit! You have a devil fruit ability!
Чёрт! У тебя способности Дьявольского Фрукта!
So what if I do?!
И что из того?!
You're nothing...
Ты ведь не...
You're...
Ты...
What are you?
Ты кто?!
Did your family treasure you too much?
Семья так дорожила тобой?
Yes. Ever since I was a child, they'd express their love for me by...
Да. Ещё с самого детства они проявляли свою любовь через...
As if!
Ну, естественно, нет!
That joke got old fast!
Эта шутка уже устарела!
Damn you! Don't get cocky!
Чтоб тебя! Не дерзи мне!
I don't show mercy to anyone who messes with these animals!
Я не пощажу никого, кто посмеет навредить моим животным!
I commend your bravery, but don't go crying to me when you die!
Я ценю твою отвагу, но не плачь, когда умрёшь!
Gotcha!
Попался!
Blast you!
Чтоб тебя!
Ranged weapons are cheating!
Дальнобойное оружие запрещено!
Then what about this thing here?!
А это тогда что такое?!
Stop being selfish!
Хватит быть эгоистом!
Say your prayers!
А теперь молись!
Part-Part Quick Escape!
Дели-Дели Отступление!
How dare you?! Blast it! Ow!
Как ты смеешь! Чтоб тебя!
How dare I what?! Huh?!
Как я смею?! Чего?!
Anyone who messes with the animals has to pay!
Любой вредящий животным должен заплатить!
You came to this island to go after these creatures!
Ты прибыл на этот остров, чтобы убивать его созданий!
Why would I do that?!
Зачем бы мне?!
I didn't even want to come here!
Я вообще не собирался сюда!
You mean you're not a poacher?
То есть ты не браконьер?
What do you think? Good, huh?!
Что скажешь? Неплохо?
It's my very own cloudy sake!
Это — моё собственное облачное саке!
Yeah, this is the best!
Ага, просто отлично!
I can't remember the last time I had a drink…
Уже и не помню, когда пил в последний раз...
You can have as many refills as you want! Drink up!
У меня его сколько душе угодно! Пей!
And I'm really sorry about earlier!
Кстати, прости меня за то, что было!
That was some horrible stuff you did,
Ты, конечно, натворил дел,
but it's water under the bridge!
но что было, то прошло!
– Cheers!
Выпьем!
Sorry for asking you to help make a raft, too.
Прости, что попросил тебя помочь в постройке плота.
Not at all. It was my pleasure.
Не за что. Я рад помочь.
Okay! Take care of yourself!
Что же! Удачи тебе!
You too!
Тебе тоже!
Farewell, friend!
Прощай, друг!
Take care!
Удачи!
You too!
Тебе тоже!
Set sail!
В путь!
Alright!
Отлично!
Buggy...
Багги...
There are many strange things in these waters.
В местных водах много опасностей.
Stay extra safe on your journey!
Соблюдай осторожность в путешествии!
Wait, I forgot to tell him about that!
Чёрт, я забыл предупредить его!
Get a move on, Buggy!
Убегай, Багги!
Look out!
Осторожно!
Go! Get out of there!
Беги! Убегай прочь!
What's that?
А это что?
Pretty...
Красотка...
Who's that?
Кто это?
What a babe!
Какая девочка!
Well, at least he seems to be saved!
Что же, по крайней мере он спасён!
He had me sweating bullets there!
Он заставил меня поволноваться!
But anyway, take care of yourself!
И всё же береги себя!
I flashily thought I was a goner there!
Я уже решил, что мне яркий конец!
There's no need for thanks.
Можешь не благодарить.
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
Ты ведь Клоун Багги?
H-How do you know that?!
Ты... ты знаешь меня?
Who are you?
Кто ты такая?
I'm looking for a certain man.
Я ищу одного человека.
I believe you're acquainted?
Подозреваю, вы знакомы?
That damn rubber brat!
Чёртова резинка!
Curse you!
Будь ты проклят!
Someday, I'll settle the score with you!
Однажды я сведу с тобой счёты!
Just you wait!
Только подожди!
This is the guy you're looking for?
Это его ты ищешь?
I see.
Понятно.
So that's why you helped me.
Так вот, почему ты мне помогла.
Well, what do you say?
Ну, и?
Will you team up with me?
Объединимся?
Sure, why not?
Почему нет?
We both have the same goal.
У нас одна и та же цель.
Let's play ball.
Сыграем вместе.
That's great. Then cheers!
Здорово. Тогда выпьем!
Cheers!
Выпьем!
Captain Buggy!
Капитан Багги!
When he was alive, I often felt he was a ruthless and scary captain,
Когда он был ещё жив, я считал его самым грубым и страшным капитаном,
but now I realize he was a bold, open-hearted, pirate's pirate!
но сейчас я понял, что он был самым добросердечным из пиратов!
Looking back, we were allowed to pillage to our hearts' content
Оглядываясь назад, нам удавалось грабить в своё удовольствие
only because we had Captain Buggy's support!
только благодаря поддержке капитана Багги!
Today, let's hold the greatest, flashiest funeral for Captain Buggy!
Давайте устроим капитану Багги величайшие похороны!
Captain, rest in peace!
Капитан, покойтесь с миром!
Please leave everything to me, Cabaji the Acrobat,
Дальше я сам — Акробат Кабаджи —
first officer of the Buggy Pirates!
позабочусь о Пиратах Багги!
I promise to rebuild the Buggy Pirates!
Я обещаю, что о Пиратах Багги заговорят!
Hold it!
А ну, стоп!
Cabaji!
Кабаджи!
What?!
Чего?!
It's only natural for Captain Buggy's successor to be me,
Это ведь очевидно, что капитан Багги выбрал бы в свои
the first mate and amazing Beast Tamer Mohji!
заместители меня — Укротителя Зверей Моджи!
I'm the captain!
Это я стану капитаном!
Hey, guys!
Эй, парни!
We're gonna test our strength to see who will be captain!
Померимся силами и решим, кто капитан!
Fine by me!
Я не против!
– Mohji! Mohji! Mohji!
Моджи! Моджи! Моджи!
– Cabaji! Cabaji! Cabaji!
Кабаджи! Кабаджи! Кабаджи!
– Mohji! Mohji!
Моджи! Моджи!
– Cabaji! Cabaji!
Кабаджи! Кабаджи!
Looks like I'll just have to fight you until your body falls apart!
Похоже, придётся сражаться, пока ты не вырубишься!
Yeah, let's duke it out mano a mano.
Ага, решим всё один на один.
I'll take you down with my bare hands!
Я голыми руками сражу тебя!
Damn you... J-Just give up already.
Чёрт... сдавайся ты уже.
N-No, you give up already.
Н-нет, это ты уже сдавайся.
– Yes! Our Captain Richie!
Ура! Ура капитану Ричи!
– Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
Капитан Ричи! Капитан Ричи!
– Our great captain!
Ура капитану!
With Captain Buggy now gone,
Без капитана Багги
the most worthy of us to be captain is Captain Richie!
самым достойным был признан капитан Ричи!
You do realize this island belongs to us, the Bear Paw Tribe, right?!
Вы в курсе, что это наш остров — Племени Медвежьей Лапы?
Captain!
Капитан!
How amusing. Are you picking a fight?!
Интересно. Решили драться?!
W-We surrender.
С-сдаёмся.
Did you find something good?
Увидел что-то хорошее?
the Buggy Pirates' super flashy pirate ship!
яркий пиратский корабль Пиратов Багги!
But who did this? What bad luck!
Но что это такое? Непорядок!
Not to mention this is an old wanted poster.
Не говоря уже о том, что это старое фото.
Oh? There's someone on the ground there.
Чего? Там кто-то лежит на земле.
Wha...?!
Чего?!..
Mohji! Cabaji!
Моджи! Кабаджи!
What happened to you guys?!
Что с вами стряслось?!
C-Captain Buggy...
Ка... капитан Багги...
I-It's so good to see you.
Ра... рад вас видеть.
I'm so glad you're alive!
Я так рад, что вы живы!
I thought we'd never see you again!
Я думал, мы больше не увидимся!
I-I'm so happy, too!
Я... я тоже счастлив!
But what the hell happened here?
Но какого чёрта тут произошло?!
Who did this to you?!
Кто сделал это с вами?!
We were punched out of the blue.
Кто-то ударил нас в спину.
It's embarrassing, but we can't remember a thing.
К сожалению, мы ничего не можем вспомнить.
The Bear Paw Tribe did this.
Это сделало Племя Медвежьей Лапы.
If you're going to save them, you'd better hurry.
Если хотите всех спасти, надо торопиться.
Bear Paw tribesmen are famous for their discerning palates.
Это племя известно своим аппетитом.
The captain says that lions taste bad!
Капитан говорит, что львы вообще не вкусные!
We taste bad too!
И мы тоже не вкусные!
I won't make a good meal at all!
Из меня не получится блюда!
This guy looks better to eat than me!
Он точно будет вкуснее меня!
Lies! Lies!
Врёшь! Врёшь!
He tastes much better!
Он гораздо вкуснее!
I'm all bones! There's hardly any meat on me!
Да я костлявый! И мясо у меня жёсткое!
Don't worry!
Не волнуйтесь!
We're the Bear Paw Tribe! That makes us iron chefs!
Мы — просто превосходные повара!
Some wine and spices will take your smell away!
Немного вина и специй исправят ваш вкус!
What do we do with this food?
А что с этим будем делать?
What are they?
А что это вообще?
I've never seen such odd ingredients.
Никогда не видел ничего подобного.
Do we boil this with them?
Может, сварим?
I just hope it doesn't upset my stomach.
Надеюсь, не будет несварения.
Part-Part-Part...
Дели-Дели-Дели-
Part-Part-Part-Part...
Дели-Дели-Дели-Дели
Is that...?!
Это же?!..
...Flashily Reassemble!
Яркое Воссоединение!
I'm back!
Я вернулся!
Sorry I took so long, men!
Простите, что задержался, парни!
Time to liven things up with a super flashy Buggy Ball!
Пора всё решить ярким Багги-Ядром!
Richie!
Ричи!
Acrobatics: Steamy Hot Spring Murder Mystery!
Акробатика: Убийство на Горячем Источнике!
Let the beast-taming show begin!
Покажем им чудеса укрощения!
Do you really think you can hit me, the great Buggy the Clown?!
Вы серьёзно думали победить меня — самого Багги Клоуна-сама?!
I have to thank you all for everything you did to my men!
Я задолжал вам за то, что вы сделали с моими ребятами!
Here I flashily come!
Яркое возвращение!
Part-Part Kick!
Дели-Дели Пинок!
Part-Part Punch!
Дели-Дели Удар!
That's our captain!
Это наш капитан!
– Captain Buggy!
Капитан Багги!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Как же мы вам рады!
I've caused you all such pain, my dear underlings!
Какие же вы растяпы, мои дорогие подчинённые!
Our pain is nothing at all!
Наша боль совсем ничего не значит!
All the hardships you've had were because of...
И всё, что вы пережили, случилось из-за этого
that damn Straw Hat!
чёртового пацана в соломенной шляпе!
By the way, who is this lovely, young lady?
Кстати, а кто эта красивая девушка?
This nice woman saved my life! Her name is...
Эта красавица спасла мне жизнь!..
Uh...
Эм...
Um, I'm sorry.
Эм, прости.
What was your name again?
А как там тебя зовут?
Everyone!
Парни!
The Buggy Pirates are back in action!
Пираты Багги вернулись!
Captain! What should we do first?
Капитан! Куда направляемся?
Get the head of Monkey D. Luffy!
За головой Монки Ди. Луффи!